Fifteen Years Ago
Fifteen years ago.
First World Collision
The purported Entrances,
tears in reality that connected the
human world to another dimension,
suddenly appeared all over the planet.
Every military on the planet
suffered a horrible defeat,
without even knowing
who they were fighting.
The Entrances vanished two
weeks after they appeared,
and the danger seemed to have to passed.
But then,
Six Months Ago
Second World Collision
they came back.
The world's governments evacuated
to oceanic Megafloats.
Only a small portion of the population
was able to escape.
The world is still being invaded
by enemies pouring in
from the still-open Entrances.
But we haven't been sitting here
twiddling our thumbs.
We've developed the Heart Hybrid Gears,
capable of fighting the enemy's
Magitech weapons.
This is Ataraxia's Heart Hybrid Gear
ace team, Amaterasu.
They're some of our most important fighters.
You did wonderfully today.
As principal and high commander of Ataraxia,
I'm proud of you.
Sis, are you seriously both
principal and high commander?
And now we have a way of making
the Gears even stronger.
Making the Gears stronger?
I'll introduce him.
This is Kizuna Hida, a 2nd-year student
joining the High School Tactical Division.
It's already been decided that he'll join
Amaterasu upon coming to the school.
This is the key to our victory.
Wow!
I thought he was the shy type,
but I guess I was wrong.
Wait, I...
What is this?!
Wait a second.
Um, you're...
High School Tactical Division, Class 2-1,
Disciplinary Council member
Hayuru Himekawa!
What were you doing in
the middle of a battle?!
I can't believe it!
It's indecent!
Disgusting!
Perverted!
This is not a game!
By sharing love and
pleasure with Kizuna Hida,
the lost energy of a Heart Hybrid Gear
can be dramatically restored.
Heart Hybrid
This is a Heart Hybrid.
Heart Hybrid...
These are your new orders:
the members of Amaterasu are to
restore their energy and power up
by doing lewd things with Kizuna Hida!
This is true for anyone else
who wants to join Amaterasu.
After joining, you'll be required to
Hybrid Heart with Kizuna.
Don't get the wrong idea, everyone!
I definitely didn't think of it as erotic!
Eros!
He's a pervert!
Episode Two
Heart Hybrid
How can you wake up later than me?
You're slacking off.
Ch-Chidorigafuchi...
Why?
I've come to seduce you tonight.
It's morning.
They talk about the
"morning walk of shame," right?
Well, maybe, but I don't think that's right.
Okay, let's get started.
Wai—
O-Okay, Hybrid Heart with me right now!
W-Wait a second.
Why are you in such a hurry?
Um, Hida-kun?
Good morning.
Himekawa-san?
Maybe you had your reasons for
doing what you did yesterday.
I'm sorry I got mad at you
without hearing your side of the story.
Hida-kun?
I'm coming in, okay?
So, I know this doesn't
really make it any better,
but I wanted to walk you to school...
You animal!
You took Aine-san to your room
to seduce her?!
That's not true!
How is it not true?!
Everything about it isn't true, Hayuru.
I'm the one who's going after him.
I'm trying to seduce him
to perform a Heart Hybrid.
I-I've had it!
Neros!
I'll teach you both a lesson!
Zeros.
Ladies, don't do this in my room!
I heard the explosion
in the dorm this morning
was Himekawa-san and Chidorigafuchi-san?
That's right!
It was in that Eros boy's room!
It doesn't make any sense that he's in the
same dorm and classroom as the girls!
This is a way of allowing intimacy
to develop between them
through spending time together.
But still, you know...
Everyone,
it's wrong to judge someone based on
their appearance and first impressions.
It's not too late to judge him
until after you've seen
if he's worthy of special treatment.
How compassionate you are, Yurishia-sama!
I feel better just hearing you speak!
Yeah, figures...
Good morning, Kizuna.
M-Morning.
Hey, pervert-face!
Yurishia Farandole-sama is an American
military ace and rich American celebrity!
You're not even worthy of speaking to her!
Now, now. Calm down, everyone.
Hey, is what the high commander says true?
If I seek pleasure with you,
will my Hybrid Count really go back up?
I-I don't really know,
Farandole-san...
Call me Yurishia.
Would you like
to try right now?
Yurishia-san, a classroom is a sacred place,
and I won't let you do anything lewd here!
So it's fine as long as
we're not in the classroom?
No, it's not fine anywhere!
Um...
Are you busy?
Who are you?
Sylvia Silkcut, Middle School Year 1!
The commander wants to talk
to you, Captain Kizuna!
This is the Heart Hybrid Gear research lab,
also known as the Nayuta Labs.
The basic technology for the
Hybrid Gears was developed here.
Yeah, that's right.
That's Dr. Nayuta Hida, right?
The super-important person
who developed the Gears.
Mom...
Kei Shikina
It's Sylvia.
Come in.
Wow.
This way.
I'll introduce you.
This is the lab's director,
Chief Engineer Kei Shikina.
Hello.
I am Kei Shikina.
You can call me Kei.
Well, don't let it bug you.
Anyway, Kizuna,
I'll give you this to start with.
It's a portable terminal that also
functions as a student handbook.
Yours is special.
Tap the icons of the Amaterasu members.
This is private information!
That's why it's special.
You can see one of the listings
is for Hybrid Count, right?
When their count gets below five percent,
it becomes difficult to maintain their Gears.
Keep that in mind.
Keep that in mind?
Simple.
If you Hybrid Heart, the count will recover.
Gear energy doesn't recover naturally?
Natural recovery takes too long.
And the energy loss in combat is huge.
So we need you and your Gear, Eros.
Our latest research shows that
Eros has a special function.
Heart Hybrid, a method of
drastically restoring Hybrid Counts.
Heart Hybrid
It's no exaggeration to say that the fate
of humanity rests on your shoulders.
Do your job as captain well.
Wait.
I'm captain?
Starting today,
you're the captain of Amaterasu.
But that's so sudden!
I'll help as best I can!
Sylvia is going to keep me updated on
whether things are proceeding smoothly
between you and the members of Amaterasu.
Yes!
I'll do my best!
This is crazy...
Work hard.
You've got a mission now.
A mission?
I'll go over the mission again.
Your job is to gather data
on a nearby island
and recover resource samples.
This is your first mission
as Amaterasu captain.
Stay sharp out there.
How can someone so lewd be our captain?!
I'll go on ahead and scope out the area!
Wait a second—
Oh, Hayuru, you're so silly.
Yurishia.
Oh? What is it, High Commander?
I want you to be careful with something.
Your Hybrid Count is at
twenty percent, very low.
If you encounter the enemy,
avoid combat as much as possible.
Don't worry. This place is safe.
Shouldn't you worry about
your little brother instead?
He doesn't seem like
he's flying very steadily...
Okay, I'll go catch up to Hayuru.
They're both so fast.
Of course.
Hayuru is Japan's ace,
and Yurishia is America's ace.
I-I see.
By the way, how good are you?
Japan's #2?
Or some foreign ace?
Don't underestimate me.
I'm the ace of the entire Earth.
The entire Earth?
Oh no, I got it wrong.
I meant the entire universe.
The entire universe, huh?
Data recovery initiated.
It will take two hours or so to finish.
So we get our samples during that time?
Okay, let's go, Kizuna!
Make sure you escort me right.
Come on!
You're such a worrywart,
aren't you, Kizuna?
The Entrances only appear on
land masses above a certain size.
So this tiny island is safe.
No, that's not it...
So, what are the specs on your Gear?
I'm not sure how to answer that.
That's right.
So what's your kill score?
Zero.
Then you're really a complete rookie?
What about combat experience?
The battle yesterday was my first.
But all I did was grab
Chidorigafuchi as she fell.
I didn't do anything else, really.
How many enemies have
you defeated, Yurishia?
About three hundred.
Three—?!
I guess America's ace
really is amazing after all.
I'm not amazing at all.
Yurishia?
Come, let's regroup with Hayuru and Aine.
Okay.
Aine-san, let's go meet Yurishia-san and—
An Entrance?!
But that can't be!
Equip your Gear, Hayuru!
Fire!
This is Kizuna!
Ataraxia, come in!
Shikina-san! Sis!
Connection Failed
Don't bother.
When an Entrance appears,
normal communications stop working.
But Gear users can talk to one another.
Aine? Hayuru?
No... why?
Yurishia-san!
Connection Failed
Hida-kun!
It's not working.
Hayuru, look!
What is this?
Blade!
No way!
We're locked in?
Kizuna, go call the others.
But then you'll be all by yourself.
You'll just slow me down!
Go!
Fine!
Eros!
Now then...
You boys ready?
Damn it!
A girl's risking her life in combat!
And I...
Yurishia!
My Hybrid Count is down to six percent.
That's cutting it close.
A Dragorie?
That's a Category-A Magitech weapon.
Fire!
My beam's power is dropping!
I can't move my hands...
Or my legs...
My body feels so heavy...
Wait!
My chest...
Yurishia!
Kizuna!
Wh-Why?
Why did you come back?
Yurishia...
Run...
Why?
Why are you doing this for me
when we've just met?
What are you talking about?
A girl's... in danger.
Of course I have to help her.
That's the only reason he did this?
Run, Yurishia!
No...
Kizuna...
Don't...
I...
No...
What is this sensation?
What is going on?
Amazing. My whole body
is overflowing with power!
So this is a Heart Hybrid?
Thank you for coming to save me, Kizuna.
Just watch.
This is my...
Showtime!
Hellfire!
This time!
What?
The Entrance is gone!
Aine! Hayuru!
Are you okay?
Yurishia-san?
The best I've ever been!
I did a Heart Hybrid with Kizuna,
and now I'm better than ever!
Hey, Yurishia...
So that means you, too, Yurishia-san?
How could this be?!
We let our guard down today.
When the tide goes out,
that island increases in size
and becomes large enough
for an Entrance to appear.
We missed that.
If I'd known this was going to happen,
I wouldn't have made Yurishia go
with her low Hybrid Count.
After her Count got in the red zone,
she seemed like she was really in pain.
Are you sure you don't
want to tell him, Reiri?
I think we can wait until you're ready.
You're late.
How could you keep me waiting?
Why are you here?
To do a Heart Hybrid, of course.
You don't even understand that?
I refuse to understand!
Kizuna!
Yurishia?
Are your wounds okay?
What about you? Are you okay?
Yes!
It's all thanks to you, Kizuna.
So...
Let's do some more, okay?
I'm first, Yurishia!
Oh my, Aine.
You want to do a Heart Hybrid again?
Well, I'm sure you do.
The one before was basically an accident!
Hida-kun, this is Himekawa.
Are you feeling okay?
As a fellow Amaterasu member...
How indecent!
Neros!
I'll punish you!
Not happening.
Come on!
No fighting in my room!
Why, you...
High Commander, I've got my report!
Illustration: Shinpei Kobayashi
Kyoto, Okinawa, Akihabara!
Megafloat Japan's the perfect
place for a date, isn't it, Kizuna?
A date?
Are Yurishia-san and Hida-kun...?
Next time: Gentle Days - Memories
Lewd!